[Music]
I am Indra.  Currently I am a lecturer
at Ubara.  I have been a customer or
participant of FWD insurance since 2013.
Until now, I have really felt the
extraordinary benefits that I have
received from FWD.
My FWD Story.  Based on
my experience, the perfect insurance is the
insurance I took
from FWD.  I took the
one bed one room program.  This means that no matter how much the
room costs, I will still
get a room with
one bed.  Will not be disturbed by
other patients.  There I felt the
very, very good benefits, namely that
I could rest completely.
So my total release to
return my activities can
be said to be perfect.  Then in
2023 I was required to have a ring fitted.
Usually, people who have had a ring fitted end up having
heart problems because the bill is usually
large.  This is very, very free of
charge because
I have already participated in the one bed one
room program, so everything is covered from
installing the ring to entering the
ICU, everything is covered by the FD.
[Music]
The changes I would like to see are
improvements to existing programs
.  As I
said earlier, I'm going with the one bed one
room option, if
possible it's more spacious for critical illnesses
than for existing illnesses.
Now there are more and more
types of diseases that already
existed but then developed into
more, ee, you could say more
severe or more serious and so
on.  That's all actually because
in terms of services, I'm
very satisfied.
[Music]